Morning's here
美…好…的…
The morning's here
早晨又來到
Sunshine is here
陽光露臉
The sky is clear
晴空萬里
The morning's here
美好的早晨又來到
Hey!
Do you have to do that? It's Saturday!
你一定要唱嗎？今天是星期六
Oh,come on!
別這樣嘛
Morning's here!
早晨來到了
I hate this apartment!
我恨這層公寓
I hate this wall color! I hate that it still smells like bird!
我恨牆壁的顏色 我恨這裡還是有雞鴨的味道
I hate that singing guy!
我恨那個唱歌的人
Are you kidding? I love that guy!
不會吧，我好喜歡他
Morning's here
美好的早晨又來到…
Stop it!
閉嘴
I will kill you.
小心我宰了你
I hate that my room is so small.
我恨我的房間那麼小
I have all the space I need. Do what I did.
我就覺得空間夠用，學學我吧
You don't even have a bed. You sleep in a ball on the floor!
你連床都沒有 睡在地上的懶骨頭
I am tired of your bellyaching.
你別再碎碎念了
I've worked hard to make this a nice place for us.
我很努力的把這裡佈置舒適
I know. I'm so sorry.
我知道，對不起
I'm sorry,okay?
沒關係
It's a great apartment!
看吧，這裡很好
Shut up! This place is a hole!
閉嘴，這裡爛死了
The One with All the Haste
本集播出：「閃電決定」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
I still can't believe you've got an earring!
我還是不敢相信你穿了耳洞
I know,I know. Who am l? David Bowie?
我知道 我是誰？大衛鮑伊？
He does that?
他會那樣嗎？
I don't know. Whatever.
不曉得，隨便
I think it makes you look really dangerous.
你這樣看起來好危險
Oh,I know.
我知道
You know what?
你知道嗎？
I never would've gotten this if it weren't for you.
要不是你，我永遠不會穿耳洞
When I'm with you,I'm like...
真的，跟你在一起時
...this whole other guy. I love that guy!
我就變了一個人 我愛那個人
I mean,I love you too. A lot.
我也很愛你
But that guy!
不過那個人…
I love that guy!
我愛那個人
I love both of you.
我愛你們兩個
I wish I didn't have to go.
我好不想走
Then don't.
那就別走
Stay here. Don't go so soon to London.
留下來 別急著回倫敦
Just one more day.
再留1天就好
Please don't do this to me again.
羅斯，別再引誘我了
I'd stay,but I've already missed so much work. They'll fire me.
我也想 但我請了那麼多假，會被開除
So? Then you could stay as long as you want.
那你就可以盡情留下來了
I wish I could.
我也很想
Oh,no. Don't start packing.
不要，不要打包
Come on!
拜託啦
I don't think you understand packing.
那不叫打包
I don't want to leave it till last. Last time,I left my knickers here.
我不想拖到最後一刻 上次我把球鞋忘在這裡
Yeah,I know. I tried them on.
我知道，我有偷穿
You didn't!
不會吧
No,I didn't. I didn't want to be "that guy."
騙你的，我不想學另一個我
Excuse me?
什麼？
Your pants.
你的褲子
Oh yeah! You like them?
喔對，你喜歡嗎？
I went to a used-clothes store and got maternity stuff.
我去二手衣店買孕婦裝
These are so comfortable.
這條褲子好舒服
Pheebs,those are Santa pants.
菲比，那是聖誕褲
Santa pants.
什麼？ 聖誕褲
Santa Claus' pants.
聖誕老人的褲子
No. They're maternity pants.
才不是，這是孕婦褲
They even came with a list of baby names. See?
你看，還附贈寶寶姓名表
These names are good, and these are bad.
這些名字好，這些名字不好
Hey,Phoebes.
菲比
So,how are the elves?
馴鹿都好嗎？
I don't know. How are the...you know?
我不知道，那你…那個…
Your clothes aren't funny.
你的衣服不好玩
What should I wear to a Knicks game?
我該穿什麼去看尼克隊比賽？
A T-shirt that says, "l Don't Belong Here"?
上面印有 「我不看籃球」的衣服？
You have tickets?
你們有票？
Mom got Dad's season tickets in the divorce,so she gave them to me.
媽離婚時分到爸的季票 就送給我了
Apparently,they're good seats.
位子顯然很好
Oh,my God! Those are almost on the floor!
天哪，幾乎就在場邊
I could slip Woody Allen my resume.
我可以把履歷表塞給伍迪艾倫
Do you guys want these?
你們想要嗎？
Yeah,we do!
廢話
Well,you got them!
那就給你們 謝謝
Just give us our apartment back.
只要把這裡還給我們
Oh,I didn't see that coming.
想不到有這一招
Are you serious?
你是說真的？
Come on. We know what these are worth.
我們知道你們哈死這些票了
Do you think we're stupid?
你們以為我們是白癡嗎？
Not stupid. You're meaner than I thought.
不是白癡，是很惡劣
What do you say?
如何？
Forget it. I'm not giving up my bachelor pad for basketball seats.
想都別想，我才不會為了球票 放棄我的單身公寓
Your "bachelor pad"?
你的單身公寓？
Have you even had a girl here?
你帶女生回來過嗎？
No.
沒有
But Joey has,and I usually talk to them in the morning.
但是喬伊有 我早上都會跟她們聊天
Yeah,you do!
沒錯
Come on!
拜託啦
Gunther,can I get two cups of chino,please?
阿甘，請給我兩杯奇諾
Good one.
很有趣
Come on. Season tickets!
季票耶！
Season tickets! You know what that means?
季票耶！你知道那代表什麼？
I'm not giving up the apartment.
別想了，我絕不讓出那層公寓
When I was a kid,my dad's company gave season tickets...
小時候我爸的公司都會送季票
...to the No. 1 salesman every year. My dad never won.
給業績第一的業務員 我爸從來沒拿到過
Of course,he wasn't in sales. But still,I never forgot that!
不過他也不在業務部 但我還是一直耿耿於懷
Hey guys!
你們在啊
Oh,my God!
天哪
We don't make enough fun of you already?
我們笑你笑得還不夠嗎？
Oh,yeah. Emily convinced me to do it.
艾蜜莉說服我去穿的
You do know that Wham broke up?
你知道「轟」解散了吧？ （喬治麥可出身之二人團體）
I like it. Emily likes it. That's what counts.
我喜歡，艾蜜莉喜歡 這樣最重要
So,how are you guys doing?
你們好嗎？
Don't try and talk all normal with that thing in your ear.
別戴了耳環還裝正常
Where's Emily?
艾蜜莉呢？
She's saying goodbye to her uncle.
去跟她舅舅道別
Didn't she,like,just get here?
她不是才剛來？ 就是嘛
Easy,tiger.
別激動，大哥
I just hate this so much.
我好討厭這樣
Every time I go pick her up at the airport,it's so great.
每次去機場接她，我都好開心
But I'm thinking,"I'll be right back in a couple of days,dropping her off."
但是我又會想 「過兩天又要送她來機場了」
-So what'll you do? -There's nothing to do.
那你要怎麼辦？ 不怎麼辦
She lives there. I live here.
她住在那裡，我住在這裡
She'd have to move here.
她得搬來這裡
She should move here.
她應該搬來這裡
What?
什麼？
-I can ask her to live with me. -Are you serious?
我可以叫她跟我住 你說真的嗎？
-I mean,why not? -You've only known her six weeks!
為什麼不行？ 你才認識她6星期
I've got a carton of milk in my fridge I've had a longer relationship with.
我冰箱裡有盒牛奶放得還更久
Look,guys,when I'm with her, it's like....
我跟她在一起時
She brings out this great side of me.
她會激發出我好的一面
I mean,I love her,you know?
我愛她
And I love the milk!
我也愛那盒牛奶
But I won't ask some British girl to move in with me.
但我不會要一個英國女生 跟我同居
Joey,you say things now.
喬伊，該你說了
Look,Ross. He's right. Emily's great.
羅斯，他說得對，艾蜜莉很棒
She's great!
她很棒
But this is too soon. You'll only scare her.
但這樣太快了，你只會嚇到她
I don't want to do that.
我不想嚇到她
You don't want to wreck it. Don't go too fast.
沒錯，別壞了好事，別太心急
No. You're right. I know,you're right.
你們說得對
I'm not going to do it.
我不會這樣
-Thanks guys. -No problem.
謝了，兩位
Just remember to wake us up before you go-go.
記得要走時搖它兩下 （「轟」所唱的歌詞）
It's too hard. Too hard!
太難了，太難了
All right. Last chance for the tickets.
兩位，最後的機會
Otherwise,I give them to my new boyfriend,Joshua.
否則我就送給我的新男友 約書亞
No,thank you.
不用了
Wait,wait. Come on,come on! Let's trade.
等一下…拜託，跟她們換啦
The timing's perfect! I just clogged the toilet!
時機正好，我剛把馬桶堵住
I want those seats. But we can't live in the small apartment...
我跟你一樣想要球票 但住過這裡就覺得...
...after living here! Ever read Flowers for Algernon?
...對面太小了 你看過 「獻給阿爾吉濃的花束」嗎？
Ever read Sports Illustrated?
有 你看過「運動畫報」嗎？
No,I didn't read yours!
我沒偷看你的
We can go to the game tonight!
我們晚上就可以去看球
The only way I'll consider this is...
她們提出比季票更好的東西
...if they offer more than just season seats.
我才要考慮
-It's the Knicks! -Screw the Knicks!
是尼克隊耶 去他的尼克隊
I didn't mean that. I just meant that...
我不是那個意思 我是說...
...the apartment is worth so much more.
...這層公寓的價值要更大
And the Knicks rule.
尼克隊萬歲
Yeah,the Knicks rule!
對，尼克隊萬歲
So? Are you going to do it?
怎樣？要不要？
No,we're not going to because it's not an even trade.
不要，因為這個交易不公平
All right,look.
好，聽著
What if you could keep the apartment and the tickets?
要是你們能保住公寓 又拿到球票呢？
Done!
成交
Let me finish. I'm talking about a bet. Winner takes all.
讓我說完，我是說我們來賭 贏的人通殺
We could get nothing.
我們可能輸光光
Or everything.
或是通殺
I like that.
我喜歡
What do you say?
怎麼樣？ 不要
Just do it!
賭了啦
Oh! I'm convinced!
真有說服力啊
Come on,man! You know I'd do it for you.
拜託啦，我也會為你這麼做
Because you're my best friend.
因為你是我最好的朋友
All right. But you can't use that again for a whole year.
好吧 但你1整年不准再用這招
I'm in.
我賭了
This is so exciting! What are you going to bet?
好興奮喔，你們要賭什麼？
We should let Phoebe decide...
就讓菲比決定
...because she's the only one who's impartial,and she's so pretty.
因為只有她沒有利害關係 而且她好美
I have a game!
我知道了
-This is great! -What's the game?
很棒喔 比什麼？
It doesn't have a name. No,okay. Phoebe Ball!
沒有名字 不，叫菲比球
No,it doesn't have a name.
不，沒有名字
What is your favorite thing about trees?
摩妮卡 你最喜歡樹的哪一點？
-They're green? -Good! Five points!
樹是綠色的 很好，5分
Same question.
喬伊，同樣的問題
-They're tall. -Three points!
樹很高 3分
Both fine answers,but we were looking for leafy. Leafy.
都答得很好 但我們說的是闊葉植物
That's not even a game.
這根本不是比賽
Shut up. We're winning!
閉嘴，我們領先
You want to finish this? We get a deck of cards.
你們想速戰速決？我們抽牌
High card wins. What do you say?
點數大的贏，如何？
-Let's do it! -Oh,I have cards!
好，就這麼辦 我剛好有牌
Yeah. Here.
在這裡
No,these are the trick deck.
這是魔術牌
Here,yes.
這一副
Okay,you guys pick first.
好，你們先抽
-Four. -That's a low one!
4點 夠少了
You look. I can't do it.
菲比，你看，我不敢看
What makes you think I can?
為什麼我就敢看？
Ace!
1點
Why are you hugging?
你們在爽什麼？
We won our apartment back!
我們把這裡搶回來了
What? Ace is high! Jack,queen,king,ace!
什麼？王牌最大 傑克皮蛋老K A
No! Ace is low! Ace,two,three,four!
不對，1點最小，1234
I don't know.
我不知道
Look it!
你們看
Come on,pick again!
再抽一次
Come on,apartment! Come on,apartment!
我要公寓，我要公寓
I know queen is high!
皮蛋點數很大
Not as high as....
但是大不過…
It worked! King!
成功了！老K
We pick again! We pick again!
再抽一次
-Why? -I don't know.
為什麼？ 我不知道
Tickets,please.
球票請拿來
Courtside,baby!
場邊區喔
Seriously,good game,though. Good game.
很精彩的比賽
What are they so mad about? They got the apartment back.
她們氣什麼氣？ 公寓都還給她們了
No,they didn't.
沒有啦
Packed while you were gone.
趁你不在打包好了
I left knickers under your pillow.
我留了雙球鞋在枕頭底下
Move in with me?
搬來跟我住
What?
什麼？
Don't be scared. It sounds crazy, and people will say it's too soon...
別怕，我知道聽起來很瘋狂 別人會說太快了
...but just think. Think how great it would be.
但是你想想，那樣多棒啊
I don't know.
我不知道
Leaving London....
要我離開倫敦…
My whole family lives there....
我的家人都在那裡 我知道
-My job. -You'll get a job here.
我的工作 你可以在這裡找工作
I always hear about them foreigners stealing American jobs.
我常聽說美國人的工作 都被外國人搶走了
That could be you.
你也可以
Yeah,but it's my whole life.
但事關我的人生
You come to England.
你來英國
I would. I really would. But my son is here.
我不行，我很願意 但我兒子在這裡
I can't leave him. You don't think there's any way?
我離不開他 沒別的辦法了嗎？
I don't think so.
我看是沒有了
It would be different if it was way into the future...
如果是長久的打算就不同了
...and we were getting married.
例如結婚什麼的
What?
什麼？
Right. I shouldn't have said "married." Please don't go freaky on me.
好，我不該提結婚的 別被我嚇到
I didn't mean it. I take it back.
我不是認真的 我沒說，我收回
No. Don't.
不，不要收回
Why don't we?
何不就這麼做？
Why don't we what?
做什麼？
Get married.
結婚啊
You are mad!
你瘋了
No,I'm not! It's perfect. It's better than you moving here.
我沒有，這樣很完美 比你搬來住更棒
It's us together forever, and that's what I want.
我們可以永遠在一起 我就是要這樣
-We've known each other six weeks! -I know.
我們才認識6星期 我知道，那又怎樣？
So what? Who's to say? Does that mean we can't do it?
誰說不行？這樣就不行嗎？
Look. I was with Carol for four years before we got married...
聽著，我跟卡蘿結婚前 在一起4年
...and I wound up divorced from a pregnant lesbian.
最後跟一個懷孕的女同志離婚
I mean,this....
這麼做…
This makes sense for us.
對我們是順理成章
Our first date,we ended up spending the whole weekend in Vermont.
我們第一次約會 就跑去佛蒙特度週末
I mean,last night I got my ear pierced. Me!
昨晚我還去穿耳洞，我耶
This feels right.
這個感覺很對
Doesn't it?
不是嗎？
My parents will be really mad.
我爸媽會氣死
Are you saying,"Yes"? Is that "Yes"?
你答應了嗎？那是好嗎？
Yes.
對
-We're getting married! -Oh,my God!
我們要結婚了 天哪
We're getting married!
我們要結婚了，天哪
Come here,come here.
過來
Emily,will you marry me?
艾蜜莉，你願意嫁給我嗎？
願意
It's a bit small.
有一點小
Damn! I thought that'd be romantic as hell.
真是的，我還以為會很浪漫
It was.
是很浪漫
Those were,like, the best seats ever!
真是史上最棒的位子
Should we give these to the girls? Like a peace offering?
要不要把衣服送給女生 表示和解？
That's very nice. Plus,they were free and too small.
好主意，反正不用錢又太小
Oh,God!
天哪
Hey,you want a beer?
你要喝酒嗎？
I know!
我知道
Open up! Open up! Open up!
開門！開門
We'll discuss it in the morning.
明天早上再說
What the hell is going on?
這是怎麼回事？
We took our apartment back!
我們把我們家搶回來了
I had nothing to do with it.
跟我無關
Okay,it was my idea. But I don't feel good about it.
好吧，是我的主意 但我並不好過
We are switching back right now.
我們現在就換回來
No,we're not. We're not leaving!
不要，我們不走
You'll have to. You both have jobs.
你們非走不可，你們都有工作
As soon as you do,we'll switch back! You can't stop us.
等你們去上班，我們就換回來 你們阻止不了的
-Right,Joe? -I don't know.
對吧，喬伊？ 我不曉得
What?
什麼？
I don't want to move again,with....
我不想再搬了
This is our apartment and they stole
我不管，這是我們的公寓 她們偷了…
You stole!
你們偷了！
Our apartment! We won it fair and square. Twice!
我們的公寓 我們光明正大的贏了兩次
And I am getting it back right now! I'm getting it back right now!
我現在就要要回來 我現在就要要回來
All right.
好
We figured you might respond this way,so we have a backup offer.
我們早料到會有這種反應
No more offers. You can't offer anything to us!
所以我們準備了備案 不要，你們搞不定我們的
-Let us keep the apartment and -As a thank you...
讓我們留在這裡 為了表示感謝
...Rachel and I will kiss for one minute.
瑞秋和我會接吻1分鐘
-Totally worth it! -That was one good minute!
完全值得 好爽的1分鐘
Good night.
晚安 晚安
-Men are such idiots. -I know.
男人真是白癡 就是啊
Can you believe something that stupid actually got us our apartment back?
那麼白癡的事 居然讓我們得逞了
If you had just done that after the last contest...
要是你們上次比完就這麼做
...no one would have had to move at all.
誰都不必搬家
Let's pretend that's not true.
就裝做沒這回事
Scarf's done.
圍巾織好了
Come on,come on!
快點 好
What's going on?
怎麼了？
Ross has some big thing to tell everyone.
羅斯有大事要宣佈
Emily and l,we decided...
艾蜜莉和我決定…
...to get married.
...要結婚
What?
什麼？
Oh,are you pregnant too?
你也懷孕了？
No.
沒有
When did How did you
什麼… 怎麼…
We just decided to go for it.
我們就是決定要結婚
We know it's a bit hasty...
這個決定是倉卒了些
...but it just feels so right.
但是… 感覺真的很對
I was just telling the guys
我正在告訴他們…
Yeah,I heard.
我聽到了
I think it's great!
太好了
I'm so happy for you!
我真替你高興
Well,yeah! Congratulations!
是啊，恭喜
I can't believe you're getting married!
你居然要結婚了
Monica and Rachel made out.
摩妮卡和瑞秋親熱
Morning's here
美…好…的…
The morning's here
早晨又來到
Sunshine is here
陽光露臉
The sky is clear
晴空萬里
The morning's here
美好的早晨
-Hey,you're back! -Hey,get into gear
你回來了 準備就緒
Breakfast is near
早餐就快上桌
The dark of night has disappeared
夜晚的黑暗一掃而空
I'll see you tomorrow morning!
我們明天見 好